Vishal Salunke

04/02/1991 • Indian • <u>salunkevishal05@gmail.com</u> • +917798424352 •

https://vishalsalunke.github.io/Myportfolio/

Profile

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the marketing and advertising industry. Skilled in Node js, AngularJS, Read, Web Development, Amazon Web Services (AWS), Heroku, Git. Strong engineering professional graduated from University of Pune.

Skills

Programming skills		
Node js	React	
Angular Js	Aws Redshift	
Express	Redux	
API	Web Development	
HTML	CSS	
Javascript	Git	
Heroku	MongoDB	

Education

Modern college of engineering , Pune university • Pune • India

Bachelor of engineering in information technology

06/2010 - 06/2015

Hobbies

- · Exploring distant lands
- · Capturing moments
- Feeling the music
- Every kind of sport

Experience

Carpro systems • Pune • India Software Developer

03/2016 - 10/2017

Project names: RentroPro XL, LeasePro XL, GaragePro XL

• **Duration**: March 2016 to Dec 2016 (10 months)

• Team size : 8

• **Description**: Clients are car rental companies over different location in the world which utilize RentPro XL for rent vehicles to their customers. Using RentPro XL clients are able to create agreements, invoices, reports to keep a track of their car rental business. Using GaragePro XL clients are able to keep track of vehicle maintenance and damages. Develop and support tool to keep clients updated with business status to analyze and grow in challenging and growing industry.

• Technologies used : MAGIC, SQL, Javascript, Jquery, HTML, CSS.

Quinstreet • Pune • India

Software Developer

11/2017 – present

1) **Project name**: Forms-on-speed

• **Duration**: Nov 2017 to present

• Team size: 3

 Description: Forms-on-speed is nothing but the lead generation forms. User lands on these pages, these forms collect all required user information, validates it and submits it to the back end. Which is then provided to client as a lead.

 Technologies used: Angular Js, Node Js, Aws S3, Aws cloudfornt, GIT, HTML, CSS. 2) Project name: VemmETL

• **Duration**: June 2019 to Aug 2019 (3 months)

• Team size : 2

• **Description**: vemmETL is used to extract data from HasOffers API, transform it and then loads it to amazon Redshift so that data analysts can generate various useful business reports.

• **Technologies used**: Node Js, Aws S3, Aws lambda, Aws Redshift, Git, Heroku

3) Project name: VemmCalls

• **Duration**: Sept 2019 to present

• Team size: 3

• **Description**: vemmCalls is call center app. It connects user on the website to car insurance selling broker via call or chat. It uses Twilio to handle communication operations.

• **Technologies used**: React JS, Redux, Redux-Saga, Node JS, Twilio, Git, Heroku ,RabbitMQ